http://www.cscf.ca/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
The Campbellford/Seymour Community Foundation Privacy Practices Policy
The Campbellford/Seymour Community Foundation is committed to protecting the privacy of the personal information of its donors, employees and other stakeholders.  The Foundation values the trust of those we deal with, and of the public, and recognizes that maintaining this trust requires that we be transparent and accountable in how we treat the information that is shared with us.During the course of our various projects, programs and activities, the Foundation may gather and use personal information.  Anyone from whom we collect such information should expect that it will be carefully protected. The Foundation's privacy practices are designed to achieve this.As a regular course of business the Foundation reports to the public specific details of all its endowment funds and donors. This information may be printed in an annual report each year, and if so, that document is available and can be requested with proper mailing information to CSCF. Anonymity is available as requested.What is considered Personal Information?Personal information is any information that can be used to distinguish, identify or contact a specific individual, such as an individual's name, address, birth date, email address and phone number. Your personally identifiable information will not be rented, sold or shared with any third party.Our Privacy PracticesPersonal information gathered by The Campbellford/Seymour Community Foundation is kept in confidence. Foundation staff is authorized to access personal information based only on their need to deal with the information for the reason(s) for which it was obtained. Personal information will only be collected and used by authorized staff consistent with the activities of The Campbellford/Seymour Community Foundation.  We take measures to ensure the integrity of this information is maintained and to prevent its being lost or destroyed. We collect and use personal information only for purposes that a reasonable person would consider appropriate in light of the circumstances.Website and Electronic CommerceThe Campbellford/Seymour Community Foundation is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of those who use our website. This site compiles conventional log files to monitor and assess activity including traffic and visits on, and related to, the site. This activity does not specifically identify and individual user without prior notice to the user through use of the site.We do not disclose information about individual visits to www.cscf.ca. Neither do we provide the information given to us on our website to outside companies. The information we collect is used to improve and enhance the content and services of the website.Contact InformationQuestions, concerns or complaints relating to the Foundation's privacy practices or the treatment of personal information, should be e-mailed to: info@cscf.ca and include "Privacy" in your subject line. Alternately, inquiries can be sent in writing to:The Campbellford/Seymour Community Foundation39 Doxsee Avenue North, P.O. Box 1146, Campbellford, ON  K0L 1L0or if you prefer, you can phone us at 705.653.2005.Further information on privacy and your rights in regard to your personal information may be found on the website of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada at https://www.priv.gc.ca/en/You can also contact:Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada30 Victoria Street, Gatineau, Quebec  K1A 1H31-800-282-1376
